I have an embryonic knob and I have a cavity, the blastocoel.
我有一个胚芽盘和一个腔，叫做胚囊。
The moment I enter the mucosa, a second cavity appears.
当我进入子宫内膜时，第二个腔出现了。
And there, I have two types of cells that exchange.
此时，我有两种细胞正在交换。
One that looks at the old cavity, and at that moment, we start talking,
一种面向旧腔，此时，我们开始谈论，
for Blechmidt, simply of an endocyst,
对于 Blechmidt 来说，简单地称为内囊，
or, in classical embryology, of an epiblast and a hypoblast.
或者，在经典胚胎学中，称为外胚层和内胚层。
The moment now I'm going to have the third chamber appear,
当第三个腔即将出现时，
it will have a new system.
它将有一个新的系统。
It is therefore a differential growth rate between the outside and the inside.
因此，这是外部和内部之间差异化的生长速度。
Inside, I grow a little less fast because the trophic skin arrives less fast, that's all.
在内部，我生长得慢一些，因为滋养层皮肤到达得慢一些，仅此而已。
If I feed you much faster and there, you will eat less fast than fast.
如果我给你吃得快得多，而你在那里吃得慢得多。
At the level of my tissue, there is an important phenomenon.
在我的组织层面，有一个重要的现象
that will appear, and there I will induce
将会出现，我将在此处引入
new information, this is what we call
新的信息，这就是我们所说的
early metabolic fields,
早期代谢场，
of permeation, of permeation
渗透、渗透
and infusion in the trophic
和输注在营养
information supply.
信息中。
In other words, an organization
换句话说，一种组织
of how the information
关于信息如何
trophic,
滋养，
so how this primitive
也就是这种原始
food
食物
distributes itself
如何在组织中
in the tissues
分布
to transform them.
以转化它们。
Okay? For that, Blechmidt understood how it happened
好吗？为此，Blechmidt 理解了它是如何发生的
and he introduced new notions that are only found in biodynamic embryology,
他引入了一些新概念，这些概念只存在于生物动力学
that information is distributed both in a way, what we call in a field
即信息以一种我们称之为渗透场、
of permeation, of permeation or infusion.
渗透或输注的方式分布。
What does that mean?
这是什么意思？
I take a layer of cells. Trophic information arrives.
我取一层细胞。滋养信息到达。
now in a much
现在以一种
more specific, polarized way
更具体的方式，以一种极化的方式
if you saw the little drawing
如果你看过那张小图
you saw that there is a zone
你会看到有一个区域
that connects to the outside
连接到外部
at first it was everywhere
最初是无处不在的
and in the appearance of my vitelline
以及在我的腔体出现时
cavity, of my amniotic
卵黄囊，我的腔体
cavity and of my external
羊膜和我的外胚层
coelom, it organizes what we call
外部，它组织了我们所说的
an embryonic pedicle
胚胎蒂
that is to say that the trophic information
也就是说，营养信息
no longer comes from everywhere
不再无处不在
but it comes in an oriented
但它以一种方式出现
way. Now, it organizes itself. I can't reach everyone, I arrive
有方向的。现在，它正在组织。我不知道是否每个人都到了，我
from one side. This side is called the embryonic pedicle. If I look
到了
at a group of cells
一组细胞
that will receive food, we find that it will arrive in three different ways
它们将获得食物，我们发现它将以三种不同的方式到达
from the embryonic
不同的
pedicle. One, the information can
从胚胎蒂。一，信息可以
pass along the membrane, along
沿着膜，沿着
the membranes.
膜。
It passes along in a parallel, linear way, it
它沿着平行、线性的方式通过，它
carries the permeation field.
承载着渗透场。
It can also pass between the cells.
它也可以在细胞之间通过。
It happens like that.
它就是这样发生的。
But there, the information, this time, becomes permeation between
但是，这一次，信息变成了细胞之间的渗透
my cells.
我的细胞。
Third step, the cell is there, which is underneath.
第三步，细胞在那里，在下面。
Now, it's the one that wants to eat.
现在，是它想吃东西。
And this corresponds to a metabolic field of infusion.
这对应于一个输注的代谢场。
Did you follow that?
你明白了吗？
This will introduce a very important movement
这将引入一个非常重要的运动
which means that we will go from completely the zygote now to a primitive fetus.
这使得我们将从受精卵完全过渡到原始胎儿。
At the beginning, we can say that the trophic information is a bit general
最初，我们可以说营养信息有点普遍
like that.
就这样。
There is no real link yet.
还没有真正的联系。
But the moment I have this passage of my...
但是当我通过我的...
We blast cells into a vitelline cavity and an external coelom.
我们将细胞分裂成一个卵黄囊和一个外胚层。
Something else happens.
还有一件事发生了。
We see here that all of a sudden, I have a concentration here.
我们在这里看到，突然之间，我这里有一个集中。
There is no longer a link with all this small tissue,
与所有这些小组织不再有联系，
these small masses and the external part.
这些小块和外部。
It is necessary to form later the placenta, all the mess.
它必须在以后形成胎盘，所有这些东西。
And this is called the embryonic pedicle.
这叫做胚胎蒂。
Or we could say the primitive umbilical cord.
或者我们可以称之为原始脐带。
It's a trophic place.
这是一个营养场所。
And there, there is this organization of metabolic movements that
在那里，将会出现这种代谢运动的组织。
will happen.
即将到来。
That is to say, if I now take an embryo at this stage, I will
也就是说，如果我现在取一个处于这个阶段的胚胎，我将
draw it, like this.
像这样画出来。
So I have a layer of cells that we will call the amniotic cavity.
所以我有一层细胞，我们称之为羊膜腔。
I have a layer of cells underneath that will be called...
我下面有一层细胞，它们将被称为……
the Vitelline cavity, the whole, here
卵黄囊腔，整个，这里
above, I can say that I have a layer of cells
上面，我可以说我有一层细胞
that will form epiblasts, below, hypoblasts, here, the
它们将形成外胚层，下面是内胚层，这里，整个，
whole, and connected to an embryonic pedicle
并连接到一个胚胎膜
and the whole is in a cavity that we call
整个都在一个我们称之为
the external coelom, okay?
外体腔的腔内，好吗？
at that moment, we see that there is a trophic source that is
那一刻，我们看到有一个营养来源
organized from the outside
从外部组织起来
to the inside, but which is polarized. And
向内，但它是极化的。而且
it is there that we observe a movement
正是在那里我们观察到一种运动
due to the polarity, that is to say that the upper part was
由于极性，也就是说，上部已经
already here at a
在这里有一个
greater metabolic activity.
更大的代谢活动。
Due to its previous position, the metabolic activity is
由于它之前的位置，代谢活动是
done like this.
这样进行的。
The information, it is done there,
信息是在那里产生的，
more preferentially first in a field of permeation.
首先在一个渗透场中更优先。
At the same time, I have a central metabolic field
同时，我有一个中心的代谢场
of permeation and of...
渗透和……
infusion
灌注
and of
和
permeation.
渗透。
But it organizes
但这组织了
this metabolic movement
这种代谢运动
to make a movement
使胚胎像这样
of the embryo like this,
移动，
that my vitelline cavity
我的卵黄囊腔
moves
向前移动
forward
向前
and my amniotic
我的羊膜腔
cavity
羊膜腔
moves forward.
向前移动。
backwards, like this, and this movement will introduce
向后，像这样，这个运动将引入
within my germinal disc an S-shape.
在我的胚盘中形成一个
That is to say that by this movement, the tissue that was initially flat, it
S形。也就是说，通过
will form a tissue that will form a movement like this. By
这个运动，最初是扁平的组织，它将
the metabolic activity
形成一个
that led to the acquisition.
代谢活动
Vitelline cavity forward and vitelline cavity backward, but in growth.
导致了收购。
Amniotic cavity forward and vitelline cavity backward, but in growth.
卵黄囊向前，卵黄囊向后，但在生长中。
Amniotic cavity in front, vitelline cavity behind.
羊膜腔在前，卵黄囊在后。
You see the flat disc?
你看到扁平的胚盘了吗？
Amniotic cavity, vitelline cavity, embryonic pedicle, external coelom.
羊膜腔，卵黄囊，胚柄，这
What is the error between these two drawings?
是外部的人。
This must be much larger than there.
这两幅画之间有什么错误？
There we see as if it were the same.
这个应该比那个大得多。
That's true.
确实如此。
It is very important, normally the error they made in this drawing, I should almost cut out, redo
这非常重要，通常他们在这幅画中犯的错误，我几乎应该剪掉，重画
this drawing smaller and make it much larger to have a more accurate vision.
这幅画小一点，然后画大得多，以便有一个更准确的视角。
Because it is in this passage, between my external coelom that is created here, and
因为正是在这个通道中，在我的外部细胞瘤（在这里形成）和
my vitelline cavity that becomes vitelline instead of the blastocoel, that
我的卵黄囊（它在胚泡腔的位置变成了卵黄囊）之间，
my pedicle is drawn.
我的薄膜正在形成。
And in this pedicle, I have a movement of permeation by my...
在这薄膜中，我通过我的...有一个渗透运动。
infusion capable that arrives ok it develops further up here
能够到达的输液，好的，它在这里上方发展得更多
it brings
它带来
a forward movement of my amniotic cavity ok slightly
我的羊膜腔向前运动，好的，稍微
less below
在下面
it creates a tilt and this tilting movement creates this S shape
它产生了一个倾斜，这个倾斜运动产生了这种S形
within
在
my epiblast and my endoblast
我的外胚层和内胚层中